# Lewis Brignell

## Front-End Developer

www.lewisbrignell.com | lewisbrignell@gmail.com | (416) 735 - 0272

$\Box$	r	$\neg$	f	il	$\sim$
$\vdash$	r	$\cap$	П	П	$\boldsymbol{\mathcal{L}}$

I'm a Front-End Developer with experience building responsive, accessible websites and web applications. I have experience with JavaScript, jQuery, Firebase and React. I'm an astute communicator who has experience working overseas and can speak French as well as German.

## Skills

HTML5, CSS3, SASS

Responsive Design

French, German

JavaScript (ES6), jQuery

Web Accessibility

Project Coordination

Client Services

REST API, Firebase

Scope, Time Management

Git, GitHub

Paired, Mob Programming

MS Office

## **Education**

Juno College of Technology Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

Web Development Immersive Certificate

Juno College of Technology Jul 2019 - Aug 2019

Continuing Education Web Development Course

University of Toronto School of Continuing Studies May 2015 - Aug 2015

Project Management Certificate

University of Toronto, St. George Sep 2011 - Apr 2015

Hon. B.A. with Distinction, Specialist Political Science, Minor in Business German

## Experience

## Media Services Coordinator | Corus Entertainment

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

Verifying, organizing and migrating broadcast media files using S4M broadcast scheduling system. Working with broadcast file servers and technologies. Conducting quality assurance on broadcast media files and logging issues using Pharos Mediator.

#### English Instructor | ECC Japan

Sep 2017 - Apr 2019

Achieved a student satisfaction score of 95% from 80+ students of all ages. Maintained student records in order to track individual progress, attendance and retention. Communicated feedback and school news to students and guardians.

## Customer Service Rep. | Teleperformance

Sep 2016 - May 2017

Provided customer service and communications on behalf of Samsung Marketing & Promotions USA. Resolved 30 - 70 customer inquiries daily. Acted as Subject Matter Expert for ongoing promotions including terms of service fulfilment, fraud monitoring.

Connect

See my work

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lewis-brignell/

https://github.com/lewisbrignell